<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alex Dunn personal site on </title>
    <link>https://alexdunn.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Alex Dunn personal site on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://alexdunn.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Macgyvering a raspberry pi home cloud</title>
      <link>https://alexdunn.io/posts/rpi_server/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexdunn.io/posts/rpi_server/</guid>
      <description>For $35, the Raspberry Pi is an incredible single board computer. You can connect to the internet, run Linux, automate your home, or make a robot - the list goes on and on. And regardless of your choice of project, the Raspberry Pi community will almost always be there for you if (read: when) you need help.
But what good is a Pi if you don&amp;rsquo;t have a good project?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My CV</title>
      <link>https://alexdunn.io/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexdunn.io/work/</guid>
      <description>My CV 
I&amp;rsquo;m interested in data science and scientific computing. (And sometimes both of them together) Right now, I develop new machine learning approaches and computational tools to accelerate discovery of novel materials (particularly for energy applications) - or in not so many words, I use computers to help find and design new materials.
I&amp;rsquo;m part of the HackingMaterials group at LBL which works closely alongside the Materials Project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random</title>
      <link>https://alexdunn.io/random/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexdunn.io/random/</guid>
      <description>Some random non-work related stuff that doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense being in a post. Probably in some state of disrepair.
TOC  gallery of dslr photos software that&amp;rsquo;s doing it right  Good software  Notion - an app for note taking, productivity, writing, ideas, and just about evanything else. Dark reader - dev reading  Photos Gallery Some landscape pics I took with a DSLR yuba river, ca
yuba river, ca</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>