<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alex Dunn personal site on </title>
    <link>https://alexdunn.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Alex Dunn personal site on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://alexdunn.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech-MacGyvering a Raspberry Pi Home Cloud</title>
      <link>https://alexdunn.io/posts/rpi_server/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexdunn.io/posts/rpi_server/</guid>
      <description>TOC:  Introduction Step A: Configure SSH Access Step B: Configure automatic backups with crontab and rsync Step C: Easily mount your Pi with SSHFS Step D (optional): Configure access outside the local network Step E (optional): Configure a samba share Maintenance and Conclusions  For $35, the Raspberry Pi is an incredible single board computer. You can connect to the internet, run Linux, automate your home, or make a robot - the list goes on and on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My CV</title>
      <link>https://alexdunn.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexdunn.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>My CV I like data science and scientific computing. (And sometimes both of them together)    I&amp;rsquo;m a Ph.D. candidate in the HackingMaterials group at LBL which works closely alongside the Materials Project. I use computers to help find and design new materials using data science and ab-initio calculations.
 Github Google Scholar LinkedIn  Last updated: 2019-05-27
Formal education  B.Sc., Chemical Engineering - UCLA (2014 - 2017) Ph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quotes</title>
      <link>https://alexdunn.io/quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexdunn.io/quotes/</guid>
      <description> “Viserys says he could sweep the Seven Kingdoms with ten thousand Dothraki screamers.” Ser Jorah snorted. “Viserys could not sweep a stable with ten thousand brooms.”
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random</title>
      <link>https://alexdunn.io/random/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexdunn.io/random/</guid>
      <description>Some random non-work related stuff that doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense being in a post. Probably in some state of disrepair.
TOC  gallery of dslr photos software that&amp;rsquo;s doing it right  Software that&amp;rsquo;s doing it right (For the most part)  Notion - an app for note taking, productivity, writing, and ideas Dark reader - web browsing that&amp;rsquo;s easier on the eyes fzf - a fuzzy file finder for your terminal emulator or tty dmenu-extended - Similar to fzf but for linux GUIs with dmenu enabled polybar - A status bar for linux Julia - A high performance interpreted language for scientific computing  Photos Gallery Some landscape pics I took with a DSLR yuba river, ca</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>